{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Rendering in React v x",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. fsfsdfd xv xcaaaaaaaqaq",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Hello world",
      "description": "hey friend",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "Differentiate betweeassdsfn Real DOM and Virtual DOM.",
      "back": "Virtual DOM updates are faster but do not directly update the HTMLhellobvvxc",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "How do you pass data 'down' to a React child component?",
      "back": "As properties or props",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "cards": [],
      "front": "b",
      "back": "b",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "hey",
      "back": "hey",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "as",
      "back": "fdfd",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": " vcx cv",
      "back": "b xv ",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "b",
      "back": " b",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "v",
      "back": "cb",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": " bxcc",
      "back": " xbc v",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": " mbaye",
      "back": "baye",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 20
    }
  ]
}